[{"answer": "It is a long -term event that has to get its act together.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "What is it and how threatening is it going to be in the next 24 hours?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "What was going through my mind when I found out you want to interview me?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Let me shorten my questions.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "I'm sorry, could you say that last part again?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "People are calling me a hero?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "It brings a community like ours very much together.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "To actually go through it, to see your family home going up in flames, to see the neighborhood where I believe your wife has lived since she was 4 years old, so many families and friends that you know being so badly affected, what does it do to a community?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's not a hero and I think a lot of people are trying to turn him into that.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "What is your view of it?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "Can you imagine -- I mean, here is this 29-year-old high school dropout, well, he scrutinized these documents very carefully and he decided they were not a damage to national security.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Jeffrey, your reaction?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "We have a national security agency to do foreign intelligence in other countries.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Should the Americans get all uptight about what the Chinese are doing to their computers if it turns out they're doing the same thing?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "But when it's normal grandpa and grandpa's phone call on Mother's Day or Father's Day?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Well, because of the technology they have, they need this enormous meta data to -- as Jeremy Bash, who is a senior official said - in order to find a needle in a haystack, you need to have the haystack.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Why should it be so all encompassing and why aren't the American people entitled to know about it?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "I think it's a terrible thought, it's a terrible idea.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Jeffrey Toobin?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Well, he was trying to get information from journalists to prosecute people who leak.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "He was trying quite hard to get to first base, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Because the First Amendment specifically refers to the freedom of the press.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Now, why shouldn't they also face the same potential charges as he has?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "No, I wouldn't.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Ben Ferguson, would you jail journalists over this?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "This is an example how much the debate changed in this country.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Isn't that what the founding fathers, Jeffrey, intended the Second Amendment to mean?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "I wasn't afraid of the gunman, obviously, I went running back out there and he was still out there.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Did you fear that she was very seriously hurt?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "We gave each other big hugs.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "When you saw Jerri again for the first time tonight, I mean, you've obviously been through this extraordinary experience together where both of you could have lost your lives quite easily, what was that moment like for you when you -- when you met?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I actually grew up down south.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "What is your view given what you've been through?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Debra wants to say one thing --", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Debra, say -- you want to say something?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Well, it was interesting because not only did he not say a word, but he walked in with his head down and he had his hands cuffed, he had his ankles cuffed as well, but I noticed in looking at the videotape later something very striking.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "What was your take on what happened in court today?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Well, it remains to be seen if the prosecutor or how much the prosecutor will take into account the feelings of the victims and the relatives.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "Could that play a part in him avoiding the death penalty in this case which may be the only unresolved thing left?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Good evening, Piers, and thanks for having me on.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Is this likely to succeed as a charge, do you think, if it comes to trial?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "It was a happy time for me.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "I first got the phone call, and I was -- I didn't believe -- not that I didn't believe it.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "What did you feel?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "Well, first I -- 10 years later I tried to get information, and when I got the nerve to go to the precinct.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "How did you do it?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "2008, I find these Background Checks.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "And what was the breakthrough moment?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "That's online service which checks people's names, right?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "No, I just put that away.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "And eventually you began to piece it all together and then you went to the police again?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "November of 2012.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "So what was the moment you went to the police?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "Very quickly.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "And how quickly was it the police found the guy?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "I guess.", "docId": "130612pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "But all from the information you gave them?", "qSentId": 640}]